Hello hello everyone welcome you all
and friends to our YouTube channel System
Wealth so today I have brought for you
200 Years and both the shares are very strong
shares I would like you to look at its
fundamentals and technical analysis
and after analyzing I would like
you to keep some stocks in your portfolio so that
in the long term
these can give you better returns than FD and
obviously if you also look at the stocks in the long term then
you will know although the
names of both have so much power that almost everyone knows how the
stock will run in the long term
so let's
start the video without any delay and I will
tell you about these two shares with some details so the first share is
our HDFC Bank PO
and many people know it is a very
good bank and the engagement of HDFC Bank
and according to the way this
company is doing very well in its financial and service
operations like retail banking, wholesale banking and treasury office
and perhaps  This is the reason
that its profit growth has been increasing for the last few years
and it has
given a consistent profit, so as
you all know that it
operates financial services including retail banking, wholesale banking and relief operations and
if I talk about some 6 major
points of this company, then the market cap,
you can see, it has a very huge
market cap and
its market cap is around 4 lakh 70 thousand 372 crores
and if we talk about the current price,
f9, the matter that
I am extracting is the
data from screenr.com, you can also go and
pack the data on it, it is possible that
what is in this data is from previous records, so
you may
see some slight matching less with some of the current data or some of the current prices, although I
would say once, do not always go by my suggestion or
anyone's suggestion,
read the fundamentals yourself,
read your technical yourself.  Before investing,
because your money is your hard earned money
and you have earned it by working hard,
so I would not want you to follow any
YouTube channel which
is registered, but in their case
also I would say that there are two
ways of doing valuation, it is
different, a
person looks at everything in his own way, understands everything, every aspect,
after that he makes an investment, so
this is my opinion, let us
see further that
if we talk about 52-week high and low, then
this of the 52nd is 13 now 5.5, that is,
around 1305, it has
given 52-week high and
its low is near 738, if we talk about book value, then the
book value is ₹10 and the one who
drinks the juice of the stock, that is, the price
to earnings ratio is 17.30,
if we talk about ticket price turning ratio, then what does
it mean once in the same  Do
n't look at the price to market of the company, the
companies of this sector, that is, all the banking
sectors, their individual suffers in a different
way. First of all, I
want to tell you that there is a P for an individual
stock or for every individual company
and you
can go to the PVR of a sector and check what is the
average
tractor, from this you get an
idea that behind this and the
average speed of the sector, whether this stock that
we are going to buy can
give better performance or not, so these things have been discussed and if we
talk about dividend yield, then the dividend is
also almost fine, I would say that it is not that
good, if not then it is the
percentage of the update and if the dividend is not
left then its percentage is given,
you should always remember that the dividend is
given on the face value, that is, the dividend is
declared on which stock,
they are agreeing to their conspiracy with a company,
it means that two  Hundred percent
on face value, so whatever the face value will be,
if there is support, let us first see the face value of this company, if there is, then there is
no
data support given in it, if the
face value of any company is ₹10 and it has said two
hundred percent dividend for
itself, then 200 50 means
you have to give almost rs.20 per share for the
year release and clearly how much
dividend and how it is calculated, you can see
that the percentage goes to you
annually i.e. in the last 12 months, at
what price did you get the dividend,
say for rs.20 share you get different,
for ₹2 share you get different and
after that the current market price, then
meeting these 200, then this
percentage that comes is the percentage of dividend,
so I am just
telling you in a rough way what is
dividend under dividend of this
value, so according to this you can calculate your  By improving the
fundamentals a little bit, we
can invest in better places and the same
return on capital is
seen. If we talk about 7.69 versus return from
capital employed, then this is when the
return and capital employed is when the
net income of our company is combined with the Chief
IT i.e. interest and taxation. The return on equity is presented to
Shiv and the
shareholders by
Aarushi. Many people
ask that if there is no debt in the company
then what is Aarushi and you have seen it is possible, no, not at all.
Return on equity and debt
turn on capital employed is completely different.
This is based on your net profit earned from your sunk capital
and this is based on the
entire VVIT i.e. morning before
interest and taxation.
So there is a lot of difference between the two.
However, the return on capital employed that I am
seeing right now is fine and
if we talk about residual growth, then this
is consistent against the residual in the previous three
years and 8.5  This 2% return given by this group has been
given by this company, so I
would like you to
look at its fundamentals once before investing, and even if you do
n't want to, you can read it. Reading gives
a good return and
our capacity increases by reading stocks.
We should look at both fundamentals and technical analysis. Let's
talk next about Reliance
Industries. I have brought both these topics.
You all must be aware of this
and there is
no need to tell much about it, although I am
giving a little bit about Dubai
because once you read it, you can
understand what is there in the stock and what is the
strength of this company. If we
talk about Reliance Industries, Reliance
Industries is also English, it is also
English
in many of its businesses and such as hydrocarbon
exploration and production, petroleum
refining and marketing, petrochemicals,
retail and digital services. So,
I don't need to tell you much about it,
Reliance is a very big name in itself
and if we talk further, then its market
cap and current price, you can see its market cap.
HDFC is above 50 points
and here the market is more than nine lakhs, if we
talk about the Everest price then the
current price is 1441, so
I am seeing it
around 2020, 2000, 2500 in the coming time and
I find it a good design only then the bank cooperative,
although after some correction,
see, continuously after Facebook and
strike and all the
problems, I invested in it, so
it has shown a question move like this,
around 90 when it was around 100,
I had bought it, after that
I peeled it for a few points, but
after that I
booked it from probably around 11020, you and after that I got out,
now later I felt very good that it
went around zero, when
last time it was at its lower level, I liked it around 98,
around 910 job, I had
liked it, sorry and after that I bought it with
zee5 and got out, but I will
say that for now  A little correction is
needed in this because in the direction in which
it has shown interest, you should let it come a little more,
after a slight correction it
can only show a good difference, it has already made its
full high of 1622,
it came and if we talk about the people then
it is 67th, this is what
it has given, so now let us talk about the hair, so if we
talk about the book value and stock last time, then the
book value of seven six is ​​being given in it
and if we talk about this topic i.e. price
to the British then it is 22.92 which is good
and I had also seen about it, on which
topic if we talk about fund dividend yield then
they have kept 0.5% dividend yield and if we talk about Aarushi return capital
employed then it is 11.69 percent and
from 11.65 the return on equity firm and from
there the growth has fallen, if we talk about three layer then
27.60 i.e.  The growth of 27.60 percent is being
seen
in the consistent growth of the last three years, so this was the
detail about this company and I would
like you to see it once and
apply it along with your own fundamentals
and its technicals and if you
liked the video then please like and
subscribe to our channel.